hi welcome back to the at homee tree hi
Slama Tatanka balladeer a treaty Roma
and thanks to shopping for translating
for me dr. McKusick apadeshi OPM went
the similar science 22 without Brad
daddy says you don't WA and the name of
this session is the necessary
firefighting equipment Tanima Cecilia
Tara Brereton Pam Adam Kappa Caron yang
dipper Lucarelli means there's a fire
here you see a picture of a house on
fire
I mean to party a tepee the scene and
Emily had camper super ooh makka pakka
actually I have been in houses that
caught on fire in the monastery one
house caught on fire so bananas empanada
Dhiru mayan kappa cara de pyaara Agatha
to do my uncle baccarat it's very
frightening salad when I gets up to a
certain kind of temperature octo opinion
nights am pursue depth and then you it's
very very very difficult to start the
fire but congrats and Gennady dead
America tabata Texas a baton do get
lucky no so let's say you finally got
this Elon Musk inspiration I'm gonna get
out of this trouble did America topic on
under his name and about conspiracies
party alone mass in a second clue order
a masala in II I want to find a cool not
stupid life saying in Amanda pattern he
took rent then Buchan hi nahi to put to
any by the way it doesn't mean you kill
yourself okay okay some cool adjustments
and then life is like magic it operati
and I'm AM Wat Pho and current and
comedian he took a thi so once you
decide to get out of the jail lock-in
once you make that decision data poquito
and remember to scan on the quarter deep
and jerry' looking at below - Sonny -
you have to study or train yourself in
some kind of path for getting out of
trouble
and are spread Geritol Malati theories
and deleted talams imagine jalan moutoku
artery masala so we're moving on to
another another great subject of the
moment dead america Pallonji tanka topic
pasar line Darryl Ambreen if the last 21
videos were successful the Godot pros at
the fitti other actions to temper has
here you and us we've all been inspired
to get out of this place and find a
better place and Aaron kami get us water
is pure a co2 clue Atari Tampa any
diamond Cheriton Pachanga peopie now
we're gonna need a path or instructions
how to get up scarran mata ki tamanna
mukhin special on Duke but don't you
planting Jericho water top a long
garrison tell apart so we're going to
describe the path that you need to
follow to change your life completely
and reach out cool Deepak I'm Angela's
Cantillon young harus under equity dope
mokuba he - panda starin ANCA them
interpret Tsubaki to be a correct
Schiphol I need this explanation is
going to have two parts Zeppelin II
pintle assam india can typically do
about coral and opal done well what kind
of Dan are you gonna need to get out of
this cycle of pain what kind of ten ten
ten means body in my bike Lapidus ten
anda akan Toluca to Cotterill in current
and return any genistein a Portland
bharati to puta this year heart of the
discussion of the equipment to put out
the fire
JME began that it is kuzey tan tank para
la talla madam can I pee like in ballet
okay support ad ballot in in Russia do
Rusia when they're gonna they actually
they actually measure children's legs
when they're like six years old so
America I can make us millennium ago
could copy and based on how long is
their leg compared to their chairs
10:00 p.m. Tom desiccant prop upon
jankoji America depending hundred
America they actually choose palette
agents start training them professor
named Amelie Panera palapa - Daniel I'm
Latin breka
so they figured out what's the perfect
proportions to dance ballet successfully
said American bonham you can proportion
porno to binary piloting and brassy
so what's the perfect body in mind to
dance your way today about to Putin
picky ransom por una manera clue our
territory to pan
and then once you get that equipment
general abaca to an umbrella to put and
picture it lungi Toshiki coral and oppa
what kind of path do you have to follow
to get out of this bucket I can burp
indica topic line young Adela challenge
and is applying harus and I could tune
to claw Terry rota so today we're gonna
start with describing the perfect body
in my diary Nikita con mammal I think
I'm and Alaskan to boot and pick urine
sample was the perfect equipment a
fighter pilot and supona
tan Bonita Karina make some how to
realize you're in the jail typical
ending and bikes but the kita Peru such
a member and I'm Larissa mobile Jinyoung
panjang then tank Tara me a typo under
Colonel think about the medina desert
about the opposite equalities difficult
the wheel of pain in one word what word
would you choose the kinda smacking
sansara derasa sake
Tellem satu kata-kata PI an icon and a
pili and it's this new to Kokoro Kokoro
a circle of life okay nobody talking
about that up agonda beach and on dune s
kita kita and a pitcher and Torah or
ayah he took the tuna it in diversity
participate junket then got be do near
disappear junkie then capilla de la hora
hora de - neow - neow anticipate junkie
then owner or Al Andalus of Moya added
each anchor
so whether you're talking about the cup
which is the whole outer world the topic
on a poppy Terrapin tanks on carrion at
the last morning in the cup which is all
the people at and a potato tank opt
Dharam junkie young Adela or or I am
tingle t2 near Ito
there's one quality that they share the
outer world and the people living in the
world there's one quality that they all
share a lasat equalities Paraguayan
Samba Antonia luetin Ora Ora akitoki
Taniya a DeSoto colitas Marika yang sama
and it's a beautiful image it's called
lungi Capuchin da da da la cámara in de
gata Kentucky yes me too long here means
the wind long dish in da prata onion
kappa means cute poverty Turk really
onion shoe means the the surface of the
ocean for example supratip ramekin
Samudra sabaki tanto and that means the
reflection of the moon on top of the
tanda bratty pan tool and bulan dieta
Samudra then if you go out on the ocean
at night
essica and dad used to take us out for
two or three days in the ocean for
fishing there's an apple cake lure is I
am PS I'm Ibaka McClure's lama to Ithaca
hurry
Terra Copernicus concur Nadia Paquito
sample under t-dub assembly
heterogeneous more than interpreter
decouple feel zero three days lama to
Ithaca Hari
sometimes there's a full moon tonight
it's very very beautiful you watch the
moon underwater then madam LM Holly dosa
in the anomaly hot coolant at the spire
they need to win a little bit of wind
comes logic ass ticket onion that that
that image of the moon that reflection
of the moon is is rippling like this
macabre bulan pan tool and pull on it to
a country club access here that's the
one quality of the world and the people
in the world which we both fear dandy
catechin disini pasa to call it Estonia
that aura around the dunya is the double
to a leha did AA magnet up sama even for
a second back on boondocks oddity our
whole life is constantly shifting and in
the world around us is constantly
shifting
saroja docket at Rose Bruford and Unni
artistic etiquette at Roseboro per kg
Kelvin duper cheap a meter per nothing
stays more than a second things things
are being destroyed
moment did Adam when atop the pit
elicited to take the Kalahasti angry
hunter can steps so that's Osama salad
the lamp you to keep that car wait day
Johnny Dukey danged timid on Tower this
is a very powerful image and it's a
little bit difficult in this cycle of
pain karate TCD at elements that there
were done japa means happiness we can
find or any money or things we can find
so Deb Kibaki Nikita but the Mucca at
Ostia dr. Chiba means the shadow because
I put Dietrich Marathi buy a gun djenka
means Jerry zdenka that special snake
Cobra and they have this ratty cooler
kosis young disappered corporate and
become America to to gooses - danke
Paula - Joe dukedom is a very very
poisonous Cobra Terry dr. Pratt the
hoola Cobra hangs on oppression no no -
la me and chain
not to mention not to not easily very
important deduct but not burn up and
things of Kali
nyan Jam is actually a sign of of great
danger ent participant Anya support and
abaya pasar so don't think about that
kamila yang sama telemetry ticket on
saya very poisonous salad Bratton and
they have a hood America Ponyo Ponyo to
cupola
and if the Sun shines dome Atari /
sinner and you're looking at the ground
that under emily has a snake's head then
and Emily had been an kepala
alert Eenie then and as a party
Oh SWAT open token in de beauté aful
circle so my champion Catania in de you
know it looks maybe it looks beautiful
punk in Tinley had indicated it's a
ticket but it's a shadow of a thing
which is very very close the piece go by
a nun schwa to Holly and Sangha to cut
youngsaeng at brat June
so we are like fascinated by oh it's
such a beautiful round shape dedicated
persona or like oh it is about deep into
food diarrhea in the theater by elevator
of snakes and extremely poisonous happy
to open up a nearby egg and dairy to to
Allah that Allah dancing a fraction by
class artist hola shopping what's the
shadow metaphor what it's a metaphor for
what happened for opinion he took
metaphor out to Papa
in Quran samsara DITA Danger Danger get
that butter such a my bus John and Leigh
Hearon but yesterday they chose Capuchin
up upon any little happiness or any
money or things you can find in this
life so Deb Kapadia Wonka - oh ha ha
young that but and atomic envelope' to
the editors Darrin Sam Ellicott padania
don't don't get close to time but
they're cutting on it to Denny Hennepin
and Coppola dairy all areas on
oppression and it has took all the
happiness you can find in this life and
all the money and things you can find in
this life have two qualities some about
yin-yang under the Potomac and on p2p
Anita Wong dance Kalahari and the tap
atomic antenna p2p Maliki two equalities
Nomar Sato look Joe
completely unimportant Summerskill ET
des panting pieces on the ground tambien
and Etana
and yangjia at the same time Yankee
really dangerous but as I attend
samozang Iturbide hyah
okay that's a it's a wonderful image any
other Cambodia in DES
then he explains it a little bit already
I'm Angela's cancer ticket Doan know
convocation this suffering real you are
born into it that padule-- partying
monetary Lima back yonder I wrote up
until tonight about the traditional five
divisions inside the 12:10 dicen America
de patata tan Lima deficit additional 32
a blast out on the litigator Tennyson
ended up at million hey one second lap
are helping Baraka humans - Tia gods and
demigods counted as one together they
are destined a devotee doomed Eddie sat
duper sama-sama sometimes they're
separated into six tanka don't break our
deepest mijn naam so it doesn't matter
these are the five choices you can be
born there's no more there's it's always
just those five today masala a dilemma
pili huntin pot under capital re
cantidad de la la la de lima - it's like
five prison cells about de lima soap and
Jarrah
and it doesn't matter which one you you
go in you're still in the jail tanti
domicile a young man I am under to chew
animosity pajara may bark in my family
Kindles five kinds of life form is like
a half which is on fire big fire my
Sigma Cinderella martini spent okay to
open the participant ur Parker a Pete
the sir
no matter what life-form you take you're
still in a burning house did a padule--
up up indicator panel
an ambien and a massive Rattata talam
luma tobacker Sandra Chapman means
you're still in a Cell almost like you
are in a cell inside a burning house
okay Chandra chupa that the other
massive predator himself and peer
support the under president allows all
to get over any attachment to this
burning house chop I look back on some
whopping on copy on a dirty room I in II
turned again China tan Turkey try to
think how can I get out Joe Papp Rafiki
okay - IPSec you are turn a Carmelite on
the key Lord Jimin Kepner if you are
able to get a state of mind where you
want to escape from the wheel second
episode a petkin cotton picker and sat
on dying and glory candidate re rota and
there's an important word here called
German Chile then a de cada panting
listen it is an abbreviation for German
bow Ito etiquette onto to man and it
means a genuine wish and not just like
[Music]
Danny Duprat apartment and to lose don t
test but the cane and Paso support iOS
Arab secular country
chica and epinephrine a ping in vomiting
rotini para occur yeah karma and
negative emotions under Harris Mahanta
can't karma then MOC negative and you
know
if somebody gave you a choice okay I'll
give you a choice the land ethic asses
are on Wembley and Eppley huh okay
second filly hundred Turk you're bad
karma or we can attack sorry eeny
kuppusamy near on karma broke under a
Tokita be Salmonella in Massena
katafanga Minaya I can add a pili
negative emotions on the camera a mostly
negative natural karma true third first
young my name is Erica petunia
yes tanah Merah cartel atrocity massacre
and if you could choose among all the
negative emotions if you could choose
one to attack tentacle and a pizza
mobility anteras more emotional active
the cannabis immobilizer to to piss
around in the kitchen a PMO's a negative
number satellite upper
yeah are you doing Saturday broken a
Papa dear Patriota SIA set it up look on
a Papa so all the troublemakers in the
whole world
some weapon was muscle a dissolute dunya
goods but I die tell em to Acropolis
MOC negative and the karma and karma
which group to attack first Club pokémon
I acted on Pepita Hulu MOC negative
kanakam about karma that is around MOC
negative which one you want me to attack
first I fell upon plump a tree poem o z-
young male and under inside
Soraka xalapa mantra tatami and
they show me table beggar disobey Kudo
and the hardest workers across the moon
we exit to eat oh they are Danny now
they are penny what kind of body and
mind are perfect for this fight
Saqqara a passion is to prove ten pick a
running sum Pune
Tarun an inning down George function
tell joseline
do you have all the spiritual leaders
and fortunes important Mitama epic on
Dominica's amongst annuitant Caputo and
spiritual epicondylitis lucky Marussia
epic on the Maliki to pre-owned to
observe fairly good intelligence epic
and Abimelech intelligent to cope I live
in a world where their Dharma even
exists
epic and I hate to be too near to Parma
Masada
and we went through this list already
thank you dr. Damon bajas dr. d-nice a
hitter say he doesn't Pune the Passaic
we have to come economy attempt at that
Bocuse to tinker side-by-side yeah I
have a fairly good life
SEPA nagi to Pinet to cope I soldier
sanction here means literally it means
someone who is keeping celibacy who
doesn't have sex cetera Harvey I to
practices or I meant asleep but did that
mean oh by the way the Scalia
oh mama acapella brahmacharya came I
became a general word for all of us who
are trying to practice Buddhism epitome
n judicata
o Moomba chiquitos my majority Buddhist
/ so we we have food and shelter we live
in a country where we can practice
Buddhism dedicated when I'm a Content
uppity la-di-da kinder karate but kita
bisa Pilate pootis MA
we live in a country where we can
practice tangled in a cotton pad kita
bisa Pilate and we actually have
available to us three important
practices then he tapenade panama me
Nikita karate and panting supper to
change
puppets education in lapa reporting
ending in lapa rubbish L Aquila parties
are called the three trainings some wine
it is a boutique ability hon what are
they
Apatow and they're called the three
special trainings America is a boutique
applaud and Cousteau Stella policeman I
have heard about the training of good
behavior that doesn't hurt other people
Santa laughing got some tongue plot the
entry lock we owned by K 2 theta
yakety or online and you know videos
they are teaching me concentration
meditation pack and a video video um rim
recognize cherry SIA
concentrated I heard teaches about
emptiness especially in the kitchen
desert lamenting are a student at
Genentech Austin underestimated up or so
my human body is not just a normal human
body I have a really special human but I
have food I have house
I have Buddhism I had those three
trainees today topo minutiae saya pecan
honey topa minutiae Norma Simon Panetta
Puma nice a sauna is Tamara William a
cannon paneer uma pinata and pootis I'm
a Maliki deaky know the exact time when
I should be getting everything
everything's ready did he put openness
cutter India telework take the putt sad
sigh husband epic and Italian years ago
dr. moody anticipatory to pursue Tonya
picture that's my opinion for tinnitus
in it that is support tonka two other
masters turn into a master cat ample
Anya he said Yemen at that Ken Campbell
are wheel of pain for many lifetimes in
committing a science de línea
Otacon parent eating ants and Alenia
detect rent eating as endearing as llama
Miller and gene e 2 theta a conversion P
dennis and dee dee dee message upon that
is Karen
therefore way don't I - maybe wait don't
go Punk in Sahara smoke antique Anya the
pencils magnetic Anya daddy
well I Sakura can apply on your topic
yes just to base to perfect
circumstances and I'm putting a zoom
rocker at the onion soup or not you're
not to all and a plethora for your house
and McKiernan parameter can adapt an
elitist the teppanyaki P or online
meditation or Amana terrible emptiness
no dioxide yeah Jason but our Luton
Danilov cyber Miller you are never gonna
get a better chance than today
I need attack on Panama despotism
pretending let me buy dairy hurry any
you have the equipment you need to put
the fire out and Emily keep Raritan took
madam can update it couldn't be more
perfect than what you have super nanny
to TTIP so loopy simple Natalie up fire
under Milliken ot Turkish Alaska a
toffee Rose no good body good home lots
of Buddhism and a virus that's perfect
Tita
the preamp I blew my young by buying a
booty sweat and fear us it to support
can and s stick it up good start to
think about where you're going nice
funky and I'm gonna make it an adaptogen
I dislike all of those things plus the
fires you are super lucky today today
America's Mahal the Tambov iris and as
pronto Harini in America dear America
three weeks talent iike Mingo track here
every American became half Buddhist
suddenly cetera America TIPA TIPA man
Jerry Stanga booties
i I don't mean they all said oh I want
to try Buddhism they didn't say that
saya tidak but America's Momo gotta go
saying Amitabha Buddha all day only one
thing Oh
America's mobile PT responding hurry
honey at the NASA to who became an
eternal blue area hapless they wanna get
out of this trouble today Teresa - panda
ito Baracus momentary stanger pootis
wreck again cluttery masala indie
and we have a perfect circumstances get
that witness it to us he has a Padma
good body not perfect but we unpacked it
does support not happy okay pop akira 34
retreats already 14 then an otaku tablet
open a clam dream suit a tea cup room
but retreats llamas polo tahun so if you
want to stop that wheel did it occur
under an antique and rota start to start
start this month
well I pull out any perfect support ah
okay how to stop the wheel ok manager a
magnetic controller we need three things
kita política ha yeah we're gonna learn
about those tomorrow Thank You Takata
and rest are three basic necessity to a
boutique ah
thank you again shopping for Athenian
democracy lucky shopping Sudirman the
tamarkan